export const QuestionsData = [
  {
    question: "How do I search for properties on Estatein?",
    answer:
      "Learn how to use our user-friendly search tools to find properties that match your criteria.",
  },
  {
    question: "What documents do I need to sell my property through Estatein?",
    answer:
      "Find out about the necessary documentation for listing your property with us.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I contact an Estatein agent?",
    answer:
      "Discover the different ways you can get in touch with our experienced agents.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I search for properties on Estatein?",
    answer:
      "Learn how to use our user-friendly search tools to find properties that match your criteria.",
  },
  {
    question: "What documents do I need to sell my property through Estatein?",
    answer:
      "Find out about the necessary documentation for listing your property with us.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I contact an Estatein agent?",
    answer:
      "Discover the different ways you can get in touch with our experienced agents.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I search for properties on Estatein?",
    answer:
      "Learn how to use our user-friendly search tools to find properties that match your criteria.",
  },
  {
    question: "What documents do I need to sell my property through Estatein?",
    answer:
      "Find out about the necessary documentation for listing your property with us.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I contact an Estatein agent?",
    answer:
      "Discover the different ways you can get in touch with our experienced agents.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I search for properties on Estatein?",
    answer:
      "Learn how to use our user-friendly search tools to find properties that match your criteria.",
  },
  {
    question: "What documents do I need to sell my property through Estatein?",
    answer:
      "Find out about the necessary documentation for listing your property with us.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I contact an Estatein agent?",
    answer:
      "Discover the different ways you can get in touch with our experienced agents.",
  },
];
